nakedpizzadelivery.com 2016-01-05

# Privacy Policy NakedPizzaDelivery

**PRIVACY POLICY**

NAKED PIZZA DELIVERY, (here-in-after NPD) in accordance with the provisions of Law 15/1999, Protection of Personal Data (Spanish acronym: LOPD) and its developmental regulations, as responsible for the website, in accordance with the provisions of art. 5 and 6 of the Data Protection Act, informs all users of the website to facilitate or intended to provide personal data, that these will be incorporated in a computer file that is duly registered with the Spanish Agency for Data Protection.

The users, by filling in out the forms of NPD and marking the corresponding box, they expressly agree to freely and unequivocally that their personal data is processed by NPD for the following purposes:

Sending of commercial communications by e-mail ads, fax, SMS, MMS, social or any other electronic or physical, present or future, which enables commercial communications. These are related commercial communications about products or services offered by NPD, as well as by the partners with that had reached an agreement on trade promotion, while ensuring the strict respect of current legislation on data protection. Carry out statistical studies. Process orders, requests or any type of petitions made by the user through any form of contact that is made available to them on the company's website. Refer to the newsletter of the website, or any other news that may be established on the behalf of NPD.

NPD informs and expressly guarantees users that their personal information in the database will not be disclosed in any situation to third parties or any outside companies or any business company groups, and whenever a transfer of personal data takes place, consent will be solicitated to the individual.

All requested information via the website is required to provide optimal service to the user. In the case that all of the data was not provided, NPD does not guarantee that the information and services provided are completely tailored to the individuals needs.

NPD guarantees in all cases for the users to exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition under the terms provided in the legislation. Therefore, in accordance with Organic Law 15/1999, Protection of Personal Data (LOPD) may exercise their rights by sending a specific request, along with a copy of your ID, passport or residence permit, if you requiere postal address information or fax, please contact us.

Similarly, the user can unsubscribe to any subscription services provided, as well as of receiving communications by contacting NPD through the means indicated.

Similarly, NPD has taken all the necessary technical and organizational measures to ensure the security and integrity of personal data, in order to prevent its loss, alteration and/or access by unauthorized third parties.

**USE OF COOKIES AND ACTIVITY FILES**

NPD on its own or a third party contracted to provide measurement services, may use cookies when a user browses the website. Cookies are files sent to the browser by a web server in order to register the user's activities during its navigation.

The cookies used by the website are only associated with an anonymous user and your computer, and they do not provide the users personal data.

Through the use of cookies it is possible that the server where the web browser is used in recognizing the user in order to make navigation easier, for example, allowing access to users who have registered previously, access areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively to them without having to register each time. They are also used to measure the audience and traffic parameters, monitor progress and count entries.

The user has the ability to configure your browser to be notified of the receiving of cookies and to prevent installation on your computer. Please read the instructions and manuals of your browser for further information.

The cookies that could be used in this website are, in any case, temporarily for the sole purpose of making more efficient onward transmission. Under no circumstances are the cookies used to collect personal information.

**USE OF IMAGES**

NPD counts with the consent of all people appearing in recognizable form in videos included on the webpage, except for links of videos of others, in which case the third party is the one who must have the consent mentioned. However, if you appear in our videos and you want this video to be removed for any reason, please contact us explaining your request and if appropriate, we will remove the video. For more information click **[here](http://www.nakedpizzadelivery.com/termsofservices)** and visit our Use of Our Videos.

**IP ADDRESS**

The website servers can automatically detect the IP address and domain name used by the user. An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer when it connects to the Internet. All this information is recorded in a file server activity duly recorded that allows the subsequent processing of the data to obtain measurements, only statistics, which show the number of page impressions, number of visits to services web, the order of the visits, the access point, etc.

**SECURITY**

The website uses security techniques generally accepted in the information industry, such as firewalls, control access procedures and cryptographic mechanisms, all with the aim of preventing unauthorized access to data.

**MODIFICATION OF THE PRIVACY POLICY**

NPD reserves the right to modify this privacy policy to adapt future development and service, legislation or jurisprudential.
